## **Sumi Han**

23-35 Crane Rd Castle Hill, NSW, 2154 0415247757 gloriahanew@gmail.com

13/03/2023

Dear Sir/Madam,

I am writing this letter to express my interest in the position of the digital/web designer role. I strongly believe that my 1.5 years of hands-on experience in graphic design and my competency in front-end languages is an ideal match to the job requirements and will bring success for both.

In my last position at AKLE HOLDINGS, I successfully increased the customer engagement with the marketing contents that I created. I pulled out 1,000% increase in webpage & profile visit. In order to achieve this, I edited over 1,000 photos and created marketing contents both digital and publishable such as brochure and banner. Also, I filmed, edited and narrated shotform videos which have 8,000 average view counts. I can confidently say that my contribution had a pivotal role in increase in our company's revenue.

During my diploma of IT, I successfully managed to achieve a GPA of 6.875 at the end of completion, while working on a part-time basis as a restaurant hall manager. In addition, I believe that quality of my academic performance was outstanding, since one of my assignments was selected and shared as a model answer by my unit coordinator. Considering the fact that I started my study from the scratch at the beginning of the course while majority of students in my course had a certain level of competency in coding knowledge and skills, my accomplishments made me confident to challenge other milestones in my career.

My determination to continuously grow and my aspiration to perfect my skill have always been solid. I am confident that I will be a suitable candidate for this position, and I would appreciate the opportunity to elaborate on my resume further on the interview.

Si	n	ce	rρ	١l١	
91		CC			γ,

Sumi Han

# SUMI HAN (SEUNGMIN HAN)

0415 247 757 | gloriahanew@gmail.com | 23 Crane Rd, Castle Hill, NSW

## **EDUCATION**

## Queensland University of Technology - Diploma of IT (2020-2021)

· Courses : Python - Scraping real time web news and list it on the webpage.

SQL - Extracting a list of desired data from database / amending database.

C# - Developing a photo editing tool capable of crop, rotate, and applying various filters. Bash - Raspberry Pi project: fridge stock management using Tensorflow object detection.

Modelling - modeling roster generating tool using ORM

· GPA 6,875 / Assignment quoted as a model answer in future courses, by a unit coordinator.

# **SKILLS**

Languages: HTML, CSS, SCSS, ReactJS, Javascript, Python

Program : Photoshop, Illustrator

# WORK EXPERIENCES

#### AKLE HLD PTY LTD

Restaurant franchise company

Business Administrator (Aug 2021 - Present)

- · Graphic design & marketing
  - Increased 1,000% in customer engagement in Instagram with my edited feed & story & reels content.
  - Edited high volume of food photo and visually optimised ordering website that result in average 30% increase in webpage visit
  - Designed and edited digital & publishiable marketing contents such as brochure and banner.
- · Accounting accounts payable
  - Managed sales, expenditures and wage data for +10 branches and published sales report.
  - Developed a new Excel template tailored for managing our weekly sales data which reduced 33% of labour cost in accounting.
  - Managed payrolls for over 100 employees and finalised STP for 7 ABNs with 100% accuracy.
  - Resolved unpaid bills accumulated for a year & resolved discrepancies with 100% accuracy.

### · Business administration

- Aided branches to get a new staff by posting advertisements to multiple platforms and successfully allocated workers to each branch.
- Changed paper-based data management to digital, and reduced 80% of paper use.

## **ICHIBAN SUSHI**

Sushi restaurant

#### Hall manager (Sep 2018 - Apr 2021)

- Worked under \$1,500,000 annual turnover restaurant with only 4 hall staffs a shift.
- Enthusiastically encouraged customers to leave the Google review and get +50.
- Made a weekly roster / Managed, interviewed and trained staff.
- Managed stocks and storage.
- Settled POS with 95% of accuracy.
- Engaged in advertisement promotion & campeign and accomplished 5% sales increase by distributing 500 voucher in the middle of Brisbane CBD.